A Guide to the Constituent Correspondence: Mass Mailings of Governor Terry McAuliffe, 2014-2018
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Constituent Correspondence: Mass Mailings of Governor Terry McAuliffe, 2014-2018
The Library of Virginia
52179
1.35 cu. ft. (2 boxes)
Governor Terry McAuliffe
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred on 12 January 2018 by the Office of the Governor, 1111 E. Broad St., Richmond VA 23219.
Appraisal
This collection has been weeded for duplicates and non-records.
Biographical Information
Terry R. McAuliffe was elected 72nd governor of the Commonwealth of Virginia on 5 November 2013 and inaugurated on 11 January 2014. He served until 13 January 2018.
The Office of Constituent Affairs was first established in 1984 to serve as a liaison between the Governor and the citizens of the Commonwealth. The Office oversees and coordinates responses to all mail sent to the Governor's Office. Constituent Affairs staff determine where and under whose signature the responses should be drafted and direct correspondence to the appropriate person in the administration. The Office also answers phone inquiries from constituents and occasionally meets with constituents to resolve problems and handle requests.
Scope and Content
Constituent Correspondence: Mass Mailings, 2014-2018, is housed in 2 boxes and consists of letters received by Governor McAuliffe from citizens, public officials, and various organizations.
Samplings of the mass mailings include letters, postcards, and petitions relating to a variety of subjects such as: climate change, immigration enforcement, proposed legislation, education, guns, religious freedom, state funding and budget cuts, offshore oil drilling, mental health services, stays of execution and petitions for clemency, Planned Parenthood, and Certificates of Recognition, among other issues.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by folder title.
Contents List
- Certificates of Recognition, 2016 (Box 1)
- Certificates of Recognition, 2016-2017 (Box 1)
- Certificates of Recognition, 2017 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Outgoing, 2016 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Outgoing, 2017 (Box 1)
- Governor's Flag Orders, 2016 (Box 1)
- Governor's Flag Orders, 2017 (Box 1)
- Official Recognitions, 2016-2017 (Box 1)
- Mass Mailings: Atlantic Coast Pipeline (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Chesapeake Bay (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Clean power (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Clean water (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Common core (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Concealed handguns (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Disabilities (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Education (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Electoral college (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Forests (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Gun control (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Health clinics (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Home care (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: ICE raids (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Law enforcement (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: LGBT (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Morva, William (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Net neutrality (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Offshore drilling (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Planned Parenthood (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Public schools (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Puppy mills (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Redistricting (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Religious freedom (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Restrooms (transgender) (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Rodriguez, Bettina Cuce (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Sanctuary cities (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Teaching Islamic principals (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Teleguz, Ivan (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Tools of torment (horses) (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Undocumented aliens (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Virginians for the Arts (Box 2)
- Mass Mailings: Virginia Tuition Assistance Program (Box 2)